[
    {
        "question": "What kind of animal is Baloo?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Bear",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Cartoon, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of the Beatles.",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "John Lennon, Ringo Starr, Paul McCartney, George Harrison",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "The most common element in the atmosphere is Nitrogen. True or false?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Science, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "The most common element in the atmosphere is Oxygen. True or false?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Science, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "The most common element in the atmosphere is Carbon Dioxide. True or false?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Science, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "What element is the \"building block of life\"?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Carbon",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Science, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose alias is Superman?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Clark Kent",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose alias is Thunder?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Anissa Pierce",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the real name of Pepper Potts?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Virginia, Virginia Potts",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which politician was the US President during WWI?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Woodrow Wilson, Wilson",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who gave the Gettysburg Address?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Abraham Lincoln, Lincoln",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the mental asylum in Batman?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Arkham Asylum, The Elizabeth Arkham Asylum for the Criminally Insane, Elizabeth Arkham Asylum for the Criminally Insane",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Scotland's national animal?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Unicorn",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sang \"Pretty Woman\"?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Roy Orbison",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "In tennis, which player has won the most Grand Slams?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Margaret Court",
        "category": "Sports",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Sports"
    },
    {
        "question": "In tennis, what is the minimum number of games required to win a match?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "12, Twelve",
        "category": "Sports",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Sports"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many pints of blood does the human body typically contain?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "9, Nine",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bones in an adult body?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "206",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the second biggest US state by size?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Texas",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the second smallest US state by size?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Vermont",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which celebrity named their child 'Apple'?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Gwyneth Paltrow",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name a Kardashian that isn't Kim.",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Kourtney, Khloe, Robert, Rob, Khloé",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays the Big Bang Theory theme song?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Barenaked Ladies, The Barenaked Ladies",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Pikachu's official species?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Mouse, Mouse Pokemon, Mouse Pokémon",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sang \"Take Me Home, Country Roads\" in Kingsman: the Golden Circle?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Merlin, Mark Strong",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "Elphaba is the main character of which musical?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Wicked",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which planet is closest to the sun?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Mercury",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name a tunnel from the Great Escape.",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Tom, Dick, Harry",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "The chemical symbol for copper is Co. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Science, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "The chemical symbol for copper is Cu. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Science, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "The chemical symbol for copper is Cp. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Science, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "The chemical symbol for copper is Cr. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Science, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "As of 2019, Robert Downey Jr. appeared in 11 MCU films. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Comics",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Film, Comics, Disney, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "As of 2019, Robert Downey Jr. appeared in 15 MCU films. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Comics",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Film, Comics, Disney, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "As of 2019, Robert Downey Jr. appeared in 13 MCU films. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Comics",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Film, Comics, Disney, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "As of 2019, Robert Downey Jr. appeared in 10 MCU films. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Comics",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Film, Comics, Disney, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "As of 2019, Robert Downey Jr. appeared in 12 MCU films. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Comics",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Film, Comics, Disney, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "What song did the Patea Maori Club sing?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Poi E",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the biggest organ in the body?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Skin",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Roman numeral D represents 50. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "History, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Roman numeral D represents 500. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "History, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which detective lived at 221B Baker St?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Sherlock, Sherlock Holmes",
        "category": "Literature",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Literature, Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "What colour do the Star Sapphire Corps use on their uniform?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Pink",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fictional cat hates Mondays?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Garfield",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many dots does a six-sided dice have?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "21",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the last three words in the original Harry Potter book series?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "All was well",
        "category": "Literature",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Literature"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the first three words in the Bible?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "In the beginning",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "An apple falling on Isaac Newton's head gave him the idea of gravity. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "Science",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "History, Science, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call a fork with only three tines?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Trident",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first Emperor of Rome?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Augustus",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of Prince Harry and Meghan Markle's child?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Archie",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the scientific name of the species that caused the Irish Potato Famine?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Phytophthora infestans",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "History",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, History"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the world's biggest island?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Greenland",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was the first full-length feature film made?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "1906",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "Science",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who likes his drink shaken, not stirred?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Bond, James Bond, 007",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name a Gothan City Siren.",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Catwoman, Harley Quinn, Poison Ivy",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which celebrity has a \"rubber face\"?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Jim Carrey",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does piano mean?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "To be played softly,Soft,Softly",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Alien, what is Ripley's first name?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Ellen",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "What rapper starred in Anaconda?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Ice Cube",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first Pokemon?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Arceus, Mew, Bulbasaur, Rhydon",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which other MCU actor featured in 13 Going on 30 with Mark Ruffalo?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Brie Larson, Andy Serkis",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which Beatles song is Molly a singer in a band?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Ob-La-Di Ob-La-Da",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a mononym for the North Star?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Polaris",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created me?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Flicky",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is my home server called?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Pollux's Mansion",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of my highest donation tier?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Neutrino",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name a Solstice event mascot.",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Cecily, Nicoliny, Nikoliny",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name a Christmas event mascot.",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Australis, Borealis, Zealandis",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is my donator currency called?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Sapphire, Sapphires",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many of my events took place in 2018?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "4, Four",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "My cosmetics include backgrounds, medals, stickers, and what?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Flairs",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can marry me. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "Grinding this command is illegal. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "You have to be level 10 to post picture in my server. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of the Three Musketeers.",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Aramis,Porthos,Athos",
        "category": "Literature",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Literature"
    },
    {
        "question": "When is it okay to farm for my lootboxes?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Never",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "I have a furry channel in my server. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many litres there are in a gallon?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "3.7,3.78541",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "Science",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of my beta version?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Polaris",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was I created?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "2017",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "Despite being associated with me, what name does my creator hate?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Castor",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest tier fanart badge I can give you?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Diamond, Diamond Tier",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What emoji is next to my server's #general channel?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Mushroom",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "A 'veteran' of my server is someone level 50 or higher. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of box do I give you when you reach level 25?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "UR, Ultra Rare",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of box do I give you when you reach level 15?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "SR, Super Rare",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of box do I give you when you reach level 20?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "R, Rare",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of box do I give you when you reach level 35?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "U, Uncommon",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of box do I give you when you reach level 45?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "SR, Super Rare",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "On what number do you get your first sapphire from a daily?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "200",
        "category": "Pollux",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Pollux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the missing gem: topaz, ruby, opal, emerald, amethyst, diamond, and what?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Lapis lazuli",
        "category": "Literature",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Literature"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who originally recorded \"Hound Dog\"?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Big Mama Thornton",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created the idea of the Panopticon?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Bentham, Jeremy Bentham",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which color is associated with nature and strength in \"Magic: The Gathering\"?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Green",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "Card Games",
        "niche": "MTG",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Card Games, MTG"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which color is associated with ambition and power in \"Magic: The Gathering\"?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Black",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "Card Games",
        "niche": "MTG",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Card Games, MTG"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which color is associated with technology and subterfuge in \"Magic: The Gathering\"?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Blue",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "Card Games",
        "niche": "MTG",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Card Games, MTG"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which color is associated with recklessness and chaos in \"Magic: The Gathering\"?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Red",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "Card Games",
        "niche": "MTG",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Card Games, MTG"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \"Magic: The Gathering\" how many creatures, from Alpha up to Shards of Alara have built-in *plainswalk*?\n",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "5,Five",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "Card Games",
        "niche": "MTG",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Card Games, MTG"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Friends, what is Ross's job?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Paleontologist, Palaeontologist",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Mt Vesuvius erupt?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "79, 79 AD, 79 A.D., 79 CE, 79 C.E.",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "Seinfeld is often described as a show about what?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Nothing",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of NASA's space shuttles.",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Challenger, Columbia, Discovery, Endeavour, Enterprise, Atlantis ",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "Space",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General, Space"
    },
    {
        "question": "Charlie's Angels usually features how many Angels?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Three, 3",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Avengers are there in their original official MCU debut?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Six, 6",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phil Coulson dies in the first Avengers film, but comes back in what TV show?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "AOS, Agents of SHIELD, Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Film, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "A pride flag has six colours: purple, orange, red, green, yellow, and what?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Blue",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Excluding a kiss, how many colours are on a lipstick lesbian flag?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Seven, 7",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who played the Knight Rider?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "David Hasselhoff, The Hoff",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of the Seven Archangels.",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": " Uriel, Raphael, Raguel, Michael, Sarakiel, Gabriel, Remiel ",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "Religion",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, General, Religion"
    },
    {
        "question": "After Aang, who is the next Avatar?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Korra",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the prelude of \"Battle for Azeroth\", who burned the Teldrassil",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Sylvanas,Sylvanas Windrunner",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Warcraft",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Warcraft"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many years Illidan Stormrage spent imprisioned?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "10K,10 thousand,10000",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Warcraft",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Warcraft"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of Daenerys's dragons.",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Rhaegal, Viserion, Drogon",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Literature",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Literature"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the episode in which Ned Stark dies.",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Baelor",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who discovered Brazil?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Pedro Alvares Cabral",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the instrument played by Reah in the first installment of Ys",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Harmonica",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "JRPG",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, JRPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Breaking Bad, what type of cancer does Walter have?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Lung, Lung cancer",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name a cat of Aunt Gayle in Bob's Burgers.",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Jean Paw'd Van Damme, Pinkeye, Mr. Business, Mister Business, Mr Business",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "What organ is the centre of the circulatory system?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Heart",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the color of Mario's brother's cap?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Green",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's the rival of Scorpion in Mortal Kombat?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Sub Zero,Sub-Zero,Subzero",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Fighting",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Fighting"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's the rival of Sub-Zero in Mortal Kombat?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Scorpion",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Fighting",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Fighting"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who composed \"Tocatta and Fugue in D minor\"?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Bach,Johann Sebastian Bach",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "History",
        "niche": "Classical",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music, History, Classical"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who played M. Bison in the Street Fighter live-action movie?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Raul Julia",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the car used by Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Toyota AE86,Toyota Sprinter Trueno,Toyota Trueno,AE86",
        "category": "Anime",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Automobile",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Anime, Automobile"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dihydrogen Monoxide?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Water",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "Chemistry",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General, Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the tallest animal in the world?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Giraffe",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General, Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the largest animal in the world?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Blue Whale",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General, Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the largest land animal in the world?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "African Elephant",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General, Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the largest fish in the world?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Whaleshark,Whale Shark",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General, Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "_____ Ito, Japanese horror manga artist.",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Junji",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Manga",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics, Manga"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is an Olympic Silver Medal actually made of?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Silver",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "What girl's name is also a Christmas song?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Carol",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Trojan War was fought over the abduction of which woman?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Helen,Helen of Troy",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many solar system planets are bigger than Uranus?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "2,Two",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many letters of the alphabet can be spoken using one syllable?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "25",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which child's toy has the real name \"Millicent Roberts\"?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Barbie",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is sixteen divided by a half?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "32",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "Maths",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Maths"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do you find the Sea of Tranquility?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Moon",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do honeybees collect?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Pollen",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which month does German \"Oktoberfest\" begin?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "September",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which month does Russia celebrate the \"October Revolution\"?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "November",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many dots there are in the Domino's Pizza logo?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "3,Three",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bones are in an elephant's trunk?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Zero,None,0",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which month of the year comes first alphabetically?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "April",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many pawns are there in the beginning of a chess game?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "16, Sixteen",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "Games",
        "niche": "Board Games",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Games, Board Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "On a standard dice, which number is opposite to 5 ?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Two,2",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which museum is the Rosetta Stone?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "British,British Museum",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is the Eiffel Tower located?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "France",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is the Statue of Liberty located?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "US,USA,United States,America",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is the statue of Christ the Redeemer located?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Brazil",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city is the Eiffel Tower located?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Paris",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city is the Statue of Liberty located?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "New York,New York City",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city is the statue of Christ the Redeemer located?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Rio,Rio de Janeiro",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is the Taipei 101 building located?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Taiwan",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city is the Taipei 101 building located?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Taipei",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is the Burj Khalifa building located?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "United Arab Emirates,UAE",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city is the Burj Khalifa building located?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Dubai",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the capital of the United Arab Emirates?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Abu Dhabi",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the capital of Australia?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Canberra",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the administrative regions of Russia called?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Oblasts,Oblast",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the color of the New Zealand passport?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Black",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel capacity of a Boeing 787 Dreamliner in litres?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "126",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Aviation",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Aviation"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the first self-propelled airplane?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "14 Bis",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "Aviation",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, General, Aviation"
    },
    {
        "question": "F-14, F-15, F-16... What jet fighter comes next?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "F-18,F/A-18",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Aviation",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Aviation"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the diacritic mark in the Czech letter Ř called?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Caron,Hacek,Hachek,Haczek",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Linguistics",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Linguistics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What metal is used for catalysis in cross-coupling reactions?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Palladium",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Chemstry",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, Chemstry"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the official Pokémon illustrator?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Ken Sugimori",
        "category": "Anime",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Anime"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the English name of \"Satoshi\" in the Pokémon series?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Ash",
        "category": "Anime",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Anime"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the speed of light in km/s?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "300,000, 300000, 300k",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the speed of sound in m/s?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "343",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21... What is the next number?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "34",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "Maths",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, General, Maths"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name a Pokémon professor other than Oak.",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Birch, Rowan, Magnolia, Elm, Juniper, Sycamore, Kukui",
        "category": "Anime",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Anime"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the best Pokéball in Pokémon?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Master Ball",
        "category": "Anime",
        "subcategory": "Games",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Anime, Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many members are in the Elite Four in Pokémon?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "4, Four",
        "category": "Anime",
        "subcategory": "Games",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Anime, Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the northernmost city in the Sinnoh region in Pokémon?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Snowpoint, Snowpoint City",
        "category": "Anime",
        "subcategory": "Games",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Anime, Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of the Great Pyramids of Giza.",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Cheops,Khafre,Menkaure",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "History",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, History"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which number Pokémon generation was Lugia introduced?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Two, 2",
        "category": "Anime",
        "subcategory": "Games",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Anime, Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "Not including Eevee, how many Eeveelutions are there?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Eight, 8",
        "category": "Anime",
        "subcategory": "Games",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Anime, Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many races has Ayrton Senna won in the Formula One series?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "41",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "Sports",
        "niche": "Automobile",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Sports, Automobile"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many races has Nigel Mansell won in the Formula One series?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "31",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "Sports",
        "niche": "Automobile",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Sports, Automobile"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many races has Michael Schumacher won in the Formula One series?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "91",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "Sports",
        "niche": "Automobile",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Sports, Automobile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name a member of ABBA.",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Benny Andersson, Anni-Frid Lyngstad, Frida Lyngstad, Agnetha Fältskog, Björn Ulvaeus, Agnetha Faltskog, Bjorn Ulvaeus",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is supposedly the youngest female self-made billionaire?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Kylie Jenner",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who went on a cocaine-fuelled rampage and coined the annoying quotes \"WINNING\" and \"Tiger Blood\"?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Charlie Sheen",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Winona Ryder has been arrested for shoplifting. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's the wealthiest man in the world (2019)?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Jeff Bezos",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Oprah Winfrey did not attend graduate school. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was a roadie for the Doors before he got his big acting break?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Harrison Ford",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the composer for the soundtrack of Streets of Rage?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Yuzo Koshiro",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the composer for the soundtrack of Batman (1989)?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Danny Elfman",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What island is Rihanna from?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Barbados",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the composer for the soundtrack of Jurassic Park?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "John Williams",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Natalie Portman's real last name?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Hershlag",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Hemsworth brothers are there?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Three, 3",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Will Smith's third child (not Willow or Jaden)?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Trey, Trey Smith",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Mario brothers are there?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Two,2",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which celebrity named their children Poppy Honey Rosie, Daisy Boo Pamela, Petal Blossom Rainbow, Buddy Bear Maurice, and River Rocket Blue Dallas?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Jamie Oliver",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of Donald Duck's nephews.",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Huey,Dewey,Louie",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the set of which film did Blake Lively and Ryan Reynolds meet?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Green Lantern",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Celebrity",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What alkaline metal can be found in lithium batteries?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Lithium",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "From which company did Bill Gates get his fortune?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Microsoft",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Christina Hendricks is a natural redhead. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was 2018's Sexiest Man Alive?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Idris Elba",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many installments of \"Friday the 13th\" are there?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Twelve,12",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many books does \"The Hobbit\" have?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "One,1",
        "category": "Literature",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Literature"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Descendants, Mal is the daughter of which Disney villain?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Maleficent",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "TV",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, TV, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has a Koala chlamydia ward named after them?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "John Oliver",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Lady Gaga's 2017 film?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Five Foot Two",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Celebrity",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who voiced Steven Spielberg in the animated series \"Tiny Toons Adventures\"?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Steven Spielberg",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many languages does Shakira speak?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Five, 5",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "How was the SEGA Mega Drive called in the United States?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Genesis,SEGA Genesis",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ex-James Bond actor died in May 2017?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Roger Moore",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the main soundchip bundled with the SEGA Mega Drive?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Yamaha YM2612,YM2612",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "Retro",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Technology, Retro"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what show did Madonna kiss Britney Spears and Christina Aguilera?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "MTV Video Music Awards, VMAs, VMA, MTV VMAs, MTV VMA",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the soundchip bundled with the Super Nintendo Entertainment System?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Sony SPC700,SPC700",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "Retro",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Technology, Retro"
    },
    {
        "question": "What company developed the Megaman games?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Capcom",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which author created the character \"Mrs Norris\"?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "JK Rowling, J.K. Rowling",
        "category": "Literature",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Literature, Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Bugs Bunny eat?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Carrots, Carrot, A carrot",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Donald Duck wears pants. True or false?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon, Disney, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "What company developed the Wonder Boy games?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "SEGA",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Retro",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Retro"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Sonic's sidekick in Sonic the Hedgehog 2?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Tails,Miles,Miles Prower",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Retro",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Retro"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who played \"the Devil\" in the Devil Wears Prada?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Meryl Streep",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Celebrity",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Spongebob Squarepants is shaped like a square. True or False?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Angelina Jolie is Jon Voight's daughter. True or false?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote Mean Girls?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Tina Fey",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the main antagonist of \"EarthBound\" ?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Giygas",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Retro",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Retro"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give one last name of a person that makes up the comedy duo \"Tina and Amy\".",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Fey, Tina Fey, Poehler, Amy Poehler",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Barack Obama's secret service code name?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Renegade",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Donald Trump's secret service code name?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Mogul",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which was the callsign of the main pilot in \"Ace Combat 4: Shattered Skies\"?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Mobius One,Mobius 1",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "What celebrity does Jimmy Kimmel famously feud with?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Matt Damon",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose mother supposedly leaked their sextape to get them famous?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Kim Kardashian",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "In computing, what does \"ISP\" stand for?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Internet Service Provider",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Technology"
    },
    {
        "question": "In computing, what does \"IP\" stand for?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Internet Protocol",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Technology"
    },
    {
        "question": "In computing, what does \"CPU\" stand for?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Central Processing Unit,Central Processment Unit",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, Technology"
    },
    {
        "question": "In computing, what does \"DNS\" stand for?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Domain Name Server",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, Technology"
    },
    {
        "question": "In computing, what does \"WYSIWYG\" stand for?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "What you see is what you get",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, Technology"
    },
    {
        "question": "In computing, what does \"TCP\" stand for?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Transmission Control Protocol",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, Technology"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was not cast in the Girl With the Dragon Tattoo because she was deemed \"too sexy\"?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Scarlett Johansson",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "What part of Daniel Craig's body had to be digitally painted on in a Skyfall scene?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Hands",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Kurt Cobain married to?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Courtney Love",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which popstar starred in Wizards of Waverly Place?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Selena Gomez",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which company created the proprietary ATRAC3 music format?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Sony",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Technology"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which company built both Videogame Consoles and Satellite Apparel?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "NEC",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, Technology"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which company co-produced the Turbografx-16 with NEC?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Hudson,Hudsonsoft",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the real name of the American Dragon in the Disney channel show?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Jake Long",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the Avatar show, how many main elements are there?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "4, Four",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What colour is Jessica Rabbit's hair?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Orange, Red",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Cartoon, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Donald Trump's first wife?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Ivana, Ivana Trump",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said \"I'm not bad, I'm just drawn that way.\"?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Jessica Rabbit",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Cartoon, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bits are in a byte?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Eight,8",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "Technology",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Technology"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Suri Cruise's mother?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Katie Holmes",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the latest actor to portray Peter Parker?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Tom Holland",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, Film, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Brad Pitt married to before Angelina Jolie?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Jennifer Aniston",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who composed \"Canon in D\"?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Johann Pachelbel,Pachelbel",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which was Mozart's last work?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Requiem",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Saigon currently known as?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Ho Chi Minh City",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography"
    },
    {
        "question": "What TV show became Ariana Grande's big break?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Victorious",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "TV",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which composer was deaf?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Beethoven",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "History",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music, History"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Julius Caesar's foe in the battle of Alesia?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Vercingetorix",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first name of Julius Caesar?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Gaius",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nationality was explorer Abel Tasman?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zach Braff, star of Scrubs, was diagnosed with what at age ten?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "OCD, Obsessive Compulsive Disorder",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Sia's last name?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Furler",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "The venom from what animal prompted Cleopatra's death?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Asp",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name a Chipmunk other than Alvin from Alvin and the Chipmunks.",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Simon, Theodore",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote the Origin of Species?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Charles Darwin",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "Science",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the ship Charles Darwin was travelling on when he made his greatest discovery?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "HMS Beagle, Beagle, H.M.S. Beagle",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "Science",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sang \"Mr Roboto\"?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Styx",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the founder of psychoanalysis?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Freud, Sigmund Freud",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "Science",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were Archimedes's last words?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Do not disturb my circles",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "Presto, Largo and Allegro relate to what property of music?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Tempo",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which instrument's name literally means \"soft\"?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Piano",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "A palomino horse would have what coloured mane and tail?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "White",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "In music, how is it called the 4th degree of a scale?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Subdominant",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the first note of a C major scale?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "C",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the first note of a piano keyboard?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "A",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the tallest dog breed?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Great Dane",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "What breed of dog is Scooby Doo?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Great Dane",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon, Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest dog breed?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Chihuahua",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the heaviest dog breed?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "English Mastiff",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "What other species's offspring do we call 'kids'?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Goat, Goats",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of animal typically travels in a 'float'?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Horse, Horses",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many letters there are in \"Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious\" ?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "34",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which movie popularized the word \"supercalifragilisticexpialidocious\"?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Mary Poppins",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is an individual having two different alleles of a particular gene or genes called?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Heterozygote",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "A billy is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A blue lacy is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A peterbald is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A ragdoll is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A york chocolate is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A weimaranrer is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A snowshoe is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A borzoi is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "An oregon rex is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A bolognese is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A selkirk rex is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A hokkaido is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "A husky is a breed of dog. True or false?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Animals",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "General, Animals, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Steve Irwin's daughter?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Bindi, Bindi Irwin",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many sides does a regular D&D die have?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Twenty, 20",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many colours in a rainbow?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Seven, 7",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many molecules in water?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Three, 3",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "Chemistry",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the special move in Chess involving the King and the Rook called?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Castle,Castling",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Board Games",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Board Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the english acronym for CCCP?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "USSR",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "General",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, General"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the beta star from the constellation of Gemini?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Pollux",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the American version of EarthBound, what was the name of Paula's parent's school?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Polestar",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which composer used actual cannons as instruments in his symphony?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Tchaikowsky,Tchaikovsky,Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which composer used an actual maul as an instrument in his symphony?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Mahler,Gustav Mahler",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the colors of Hatsune Miku's panties?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Blue and White,White and Blue,Teal and White,White and Teal",
        "category": "Anime",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "Weeb Stuff",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Anime, Music, Weeb Stuff"
    },
    {
        "question": "What number represents \"death\" in Japanese?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Four,4",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "History",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General, History"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the most successful member of the Jackson 5?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Michael, Michael  Jackson",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose band/back-up was 'the Supremes'?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Diana Ross",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the plastic end of a shoelace called?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Aglet",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sings 'All I Want For Christmas Is You'?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Mariah Carey",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose life is La Vie En Rose based on?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Edith Piaf",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "The film where Leonardo DiCaprio helps manipulate someone's mind via their dreams is called Deception. True or false?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Film, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of the wives in Mad Max: Fury Road.",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "The Splendid Angharad, Capable, Cheedo the Fragile, Toast the Knowing, the Dag",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many planets in the Solar System does have rings?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Four,4",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many planets in the Solar System does NOT have rings?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Four,4",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science"
    },
    {
        "question": "Message in a Bottle",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "The Police",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Retro",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Retro"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of the games that pioneered the \"Looter Shooter\" genre",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Borderlands,Destiny",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is used as savepoint in the Dark Souls games?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Bonfire",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the real name of the Shinobi from SEGA's Shinobi series?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Joe Musashi",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Retro",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Retro"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of the protagonists of the first Golden Axe game.",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Ax Battler,Tyris Flare,Gillius Thunderhead",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Retro",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Retro"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the Madonna lyric: Papa don't preach, I'm in trouble deep, Papa don't preach . . . (4 words)",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "I've been losing sleep, I been losin' sleep, I've been losin' sleep, I been losing sleep",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the Van Morrison lyric: In the misty morning fog with, Our hearts a thumpin' and you . . . (3 words)",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "My brown-eyed girl",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the Little Mix lyric: No matter what you say it won't hurt me, Don't matter if I fall from the sky . . . (6 words)",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "These wings are made to fly",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the Justin Bieber lyric: And I'm like baby, baby, baby oh, Like baby, baby, baby no . . . (5 words)",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Like baby, baby, baby oh",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the Beatles lyric: Cellophane flowers of yellow and green, Towering over your head, Look for the girl with the sun in her eyes . . . (3 words)",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "And she's gone",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the Backstreet Boys lyric: Backstreet's back . . . (1 word)",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "ALRIGHT",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the David Bowie lyric: Am I sitting in a tin can, Far above the world, Planet Earth is blue . . . (6 words)",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "And there's nothing I can do",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the Luis Fonsi lyric: Des - pa - . . . (1 word)",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "cito",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the Nicki Minaj lyric: Might spend a couple thou just to bust that open, Rip it off no joking . . . (5 words)",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Like your name Hulk Hogan",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the Sir-Mix-A-Lot lyric: MY ANACONDA . . . (1 word)",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "DON'T",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Russia's greatest love machine?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Rasputin",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the genius behind Crazy Frog?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Axel F",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did Elvis go when his heart was broken?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Heartbreak Hotel",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "HAIM sampled which Eagles song to make 'The Wire'?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Heartache Tonight",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Chaos Emeralds are there?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Seven,7",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "Retro",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Retro"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's bad?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Michael Jackson",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which musician is famous for parodying other artists' songs?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Weird Al, Weird Al Yankovic",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Weird Al Yankovic's favoured instrument?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Accordion",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which rapper was featured on Justin Bieber's 'Baby'?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Usher",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What penguin documentary did Morgan Freeman narrate?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "March of the Penguins",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Michael Jackson die?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "2009",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "Music",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity, Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year were the LA riots?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "1992",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "Corsica was the first country to give women the right to vote. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "History, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "New Zealand was the first country to give women the right to vote without revoking it. True or false?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "History, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of the primary five countries in the Maghreb.",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Morocco, Tunisia, Libya, Mauritania, Algeria",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the villain alias of Scarlet Witch's father?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Magneto",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the villain alias of Polaris's father?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Magneto",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which X-Man had the power to be immediately forgotten?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "ForgetMeNot",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What metal coats Wolverine's skeleton?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Adamantium",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What metal is Captain America's shield made out of?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Vibranium",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "From which country does vibranium originate?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Wakanda",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Storm from X-Men was queen of which country?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Wakanda",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many children do Sue Storm and Reed Richards have?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "2, Two",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fabled classification above Alpha mutants in X-Men?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Omega",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the divide between the Avengers over superhero registration?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Civil War",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "In an alternate universe, Iron Man and Captain America married. What was Iron Man's first name then?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Natasha",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Captain America's squad in WWII?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "The Howling Commandos, Howling Commandos",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the alias of Lightning's father?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Black Lightning",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is this accent ~ called?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Tilde",
        "category": "General",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "General"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character's death is considered to mark the end of the Silver Age of Comics?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Gwen Stacey",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which S.H.I.E.L.D. Director wears an eyepatch?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Fury, Nick Fury, Director Fury",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose mental breakdown caused the House of M storyline, where many mutants lost their powers?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Scarlet Witch",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero was known as 'Coma Girl' to Peter Parker in high school?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Jessica Jones",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who played Jean Grey in the Dark Phoenix film?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Sophie Turner",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Comics",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Batman's mother's name?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Martha Wayne",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kitty Pryde's first alias was Phaser. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Comics, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the cat who became a Red Lantern?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Dex-Starr",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Superman is faster than the Flash. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Comics, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Starfire has three siblings, Blackfire, Wildfire, and Darkfire. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Comics, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Starfire has two siblings, Blackfire and Wildfire. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Comics, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Starfire has two siblings, Blackfire and Darkfire. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "TRUE",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Comics, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Starfire has two siblings, Wildfire and Darkfire. True or false?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Comics, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Along with Terry Pratchett, who wrote Good Omens?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Neil Gaiman",
        "category": "Literature",
        "subcategory": "TV",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Literature, TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "There are six infinity stones: time, soul, reality, space, mind, and what?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Power",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Wonder Woman's alias?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Diana Prince",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Batman's nemesis?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "The Joker, Joker",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Superman's nemesis?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Lex Luthor",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What word does Billy Batson say to get incredible powers?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "SHAZAM",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you mix the two colours of Harley Quinn's pigtails, what do you get?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Purple",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Poison Ivy fears she might accidentally poison Harley Quinn at any time with her powers. True or false?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "FALSE",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "TF",
        "allcats": "Comics, TF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kara Zor-El is better known as what?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Supergirl",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What colour is Beast Boy's skin?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Green",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name Raven's demonic father.",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Trigon",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the mother of Bruce Wayne's son.",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Talia al Ghul",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the surname of Batman's butler?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Pennyworth",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first alias of Commissioner Gordon's daughter?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Batgirl",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the second alias of Commissioner Gordon's daughter?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Oracle",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the shapeshifting refugee species in the MCU?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Skrull, Skrulls",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Comics",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the superhero alias of Daisy Johnson?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Quake",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "TV",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics, TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Koriand'r?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Starfire",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Oliver Queen's weapon of choice?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Bow and Arrow",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Doom Patrol is a spin-off of what other DC TV show?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Titans",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Comics",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does the Phoenix Force most famously inhabit?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Jean Grey",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Carol Danvers's job before she became a superhero?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Pilot, Air Force Pilot",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics, Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the five senses does Daredevil lack?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Sight",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "TV",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics, TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one of the four Defenders.",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Luke Cage, Jessica Jones, Matt Murdock, Daredevil, Iron Fist, Danny Rand",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "TV",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics, TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "What piece of jewelry does a Green Lantern wear?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Ring",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Storm sibling is part of the Fantastic Four along with Sue?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Johnny, Johnny Storm",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics, Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "What number wall does Deadpool keep breaking?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "4, 4th, Four, Fourth",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics, Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Deadpool wish he was in a relationship with?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Spidey, Spider-Man, Spider Man, Spiderman, Peter Parker",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Deadpool has claimed he is a mix of Ryan Reynolds and which breed of dog?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Sharpei, Shar-Pei, Shar Pei",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one real name of the duo Cloak and Dagger.",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Tandy Bowen Tyrone Johnson",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "TV",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics, TV"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the institution the Black Widow was raised in?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "The Red Room, Red Room",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "Film",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics, Film"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Thor's father?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Odin",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Loki's real father?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Laufey",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Remy LeBeau's weapon of choice?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Cards, Playing Cards, Deck of Cards Decks of Cards",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is X-23 a clone of?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Wolverine, Logan",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the real name of the blue shapeshifting mutant that helps Magneto?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Raven Darkhölme, Raven Darkholme",
        "category": "Comics",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Comics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What male vocal range sits between bass and tenor?",
        "level": 4,
        "answer": "Baritone",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which actress is Kate Hudson's mother?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Goldie Hawn",
        "category": "Celebrity",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Celebrity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who drove his chevy to the levy, but it was dry?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Don McLean",
        "category": "Music",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Music"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who orchestrated Sharon Tate's death?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Charles Manson",
        "category": "History",
        "subcategory": "",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "History"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the main antagonist in \"Phineas & Ferb\"?",
        "level": 1,
        "answer": "Heinz, Doofenshmirtz, Heinz Doofenshmirtz",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created the Periodic Table of Elements?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Dmitri Mendeleev, Dmitri Ivanovich Mendeleev, Mendeleev",
        "category": "Science",
        "subcategory": "Chemistry",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Science, Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the capital of New Zealand before the current one?",
        "level": 5,
        "answer": "Auckland",
        "category": "Geography",
        "subcategory": "History",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Geography, History"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which studio developed \"Hill Climb Racing\"?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Fingersoft",
        "category": "Games",
        "subcategory": "Mobile",
        "niche": "Android",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Games, Mobile, Android"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Academy Awards did the musical Frozen win?",
        "level": 3,
        "answer": "Two, 2",
        "category": "Film",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "Disney",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "Film, Cartoon, Disney"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sang the \"What's New, Scooby Doo?\" theme?",
        "level": 2,
        "answer": "Simple Plan",
        "category": "TV",
        "subcategory": "Cartoon",
        "niche": "",
        "type": "",
        "allcats": "TV, Cartoon"
    }
]
